## Hello

# I'm Sheldon Stevens

1450 E Bell rd, Apt 1088 Phoenix, AZ 85022 623-282-5901 sgste080@yahoo.com

# **About Me**

I am a nursing student with a positive and uplifting attitude. I manage my time effectively to ensure completion of daily and additional tasks. I also keep my composure when working under demanding conditions and handling conflict. Covid has affected both my work and my education. Although times have been tough and my life has been put on hold, I am going to keep pushing forward in hopes to find a new and exciting opportunity that could potentially be a long lasting career.

### Skills

I am proficient in time management, customer service and appreciation, and computer skills. I have a huge drive to be successful and I am a quick learner and a strong team member.

#### Experience

March 2020 - current

**Tutor Time** - Assistant Preschool Teacher

- Assisting with the development of children ages 0-12 years old.
- Assisting with curriculum planning and execution.
- Leading fun and creative physical and educational activities.
- Ensuring I am very time oriented.

November 2017- March 2020

**Amazon - tusı -** *Ambassador* 

- Making sure that all customer returns get processed correctly and efficiently in several different departments.
- Training numerous new associates on proper safety and procedures within different departments.
- Assisting in the development of special projects throughout the warehouse to ensure our procedures are as safe and effective as they can be.
- Overseeing parts of different departments including team and mech, customer returns, the dock/ TDR, warehouse deals and safety.

## Education

April 2018- Current

Carrington College- 2149 W Dunlap Ave Unit 100 Phoenix, AZ 85021

- Nursing.